[
    {
        "question": "In what year was Minecraft fully released?",
        "answerA": 2012,
        "answerB": 2011,
        "answerC": 2007,
        "answerD": 2010,
        "correct": 1
    }, {
        "question": "How many players can play together, at the same time, on Minecraft Realms?", 
        "answerA": 12,
        "answerB": 8,
        "answerC": 11,
        "answerD": 10,
        "correct": 3
    }, {
        "question": "The game follows a day and night cycle. How long does one full cycle last in real-time?",
        "answerA": "20 minutes",
        "answerB": "30 minutes",
        "answerC": "60 minutes",
        "answerD": "10 minutes",
        "correct": 0
    }, {
        "question": "Which of the following cannot be tamed?",
        "answerA": "Wolf",
        "answerB": "Ocelot",
        "answerC": "Chicken",
        "answerD": "Horse",
        "correct": 2
    },/* {
        "question": "What item do you need to make all of the potions?",
        "answerA" "Water bottle",
        "answerB": "Gun powder",
        "answerC": "Blaze Powder",
        "answerD": "Nether Wart",
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "Which species began due to a coding error?",
        "answerA": "Slime",
        "answerB": "Piglin",
        "answerC": "Drowned"
        "answerD": "Creeper",
        "correct" 3
    },{
        "question": "What must you use to mine ores and stones?",
        "answerA": "Iron Pickaxe",
        "answerB": "Axe",
        "answerC": "Stone Pickaxe"
        "answerD": "Wooden Pickaxe"
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "To make one iron ingot, how many slabs of iron ore do you need?",
        "answerA": 2,
        "answerB": 0,
        "answerC": 1,
        "answerD": 5,
        "correct": 2
    },{
        "question": "Axolotl can come in how many different colors?",
        "answerA": 5,
        "answerB": 6,
        "answerC": 2,
        "answerD": 7,
        "correct": 0
    },{
        "question": "Which creature has 2 hearts?",
        "answerA": "Chicken",
        "answerB": "Fish",
        "answerC": "Rabbit",
        "answerD": "Pig",
        "correct": 0
    }*/
    ]
